Viewers, we declare you free from whatever sickness or disease
in your blood, fluids, kidneys, tendons or liver.
Be declared free, in the name of Jesus!
Whatever you might have taken in your dreams,
I flush them out, in the name of Jesus!
Flush them out by the power of the Holy Ghost!
Holy Ghost!
Begin to flush them out, in the name of Jesus! Prayer!
Whatever poison you might have taken through dreams,
flush them out by the blood of Jesus and power of the Holy Ghost!
Holy Ghost!
Flush them out!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers all over the world, receive clearance!
In the name of Jesus!
Health clearance!
Business clearance!
Finances clearance!
Marriage clearance, in the name of Jesus!
Clearance!
In Jesus' name!
Thank You, Lord!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Rejoice!